Hmm, where's Kazuto?
He should have shown up by now.
Maybe they don't have all the
battles up on the feet yet.
I mean, knowing Kirito,
we should have seen him running
around guns blazing from the start.
I don't know.
He's one of the craftiest
players I've ever met.
He's probably laying low somewhere waiting
for the competition to
kill each other off.
Oh, please.
You and I both know he
doesn't play like that.
Isn't that right, Yui?
Absolutely.
Besides that, he's so fast, I
doubt he'll even show up on camera.
He'll sneak up and strike before
his enemy knows what's happening.
He can't do it any other way.
I mean, it's a game with
guns and he's using a sword.
What a dupe thing.
He's kind of a dork.
That one guy's unbelievable.
You mean the one in white?
Oh, he's super fast.
Yeah, that guy's sick.
I bet he's going to win this thing.
Looks like your boy's full of suck, Liz.
Shut up, he's not out of it yet.
What happened to him?
It's some kind of paralysis attack.
Most likely temporary.
It's like he was hit with
that wind spell, Thunderweb.
Uh...
Malawatsuri ma.
Muzun Dark no Sugou wo.
So no te de uchi harate.
Ikonleta namiida no nukumori de.
I'm not going to die.
Xenon, shoot. Huh? Which one?
It's the guy in the cloak.
There's no time.
Shoot him. Hurry.
Don't let him fire that gun.
Oh.
Oh, crap.
He knew I was here.
How could he?
Maybe he spotted me earlier.
Got my position from the last scan.
Jesus, what was that?
Death Gun is my name,
and the name of my gun.
One day,
I'll pay you all a visit too,
and bring real death with this gun.
You've seen my power it
is real this isn't over
not yet I'm just getting
Started it's showtime
I've met that person before but where
there's only one place I could have
I'm Grad.
Way to scare the hell out of everyone.
You gotta be kidding me. No way. Can't be.
You know him too?
Do you remember his name?
No.
I forget the handle he used, but it's him.
There's no doubt.
He was in Laughing Coffin.
Laughing Coffin.
Was he their leader?
You know, the knife-wielder?
No, I'm pretty sure it's not Pooh.
Something about the way this
guy talks and acts is different.
Except for that show timeline, though.
Pooh was the only one who said that.
But this guy, he was close to Pooh.
I'm talking right-hand man close.
Kirito.
It's him, all right.
Oh, yeah. That's Death Gun. Death Gun?
You're joking.
You mean those rumors about players
getting shot and disappearing,
those are all true?
Yeah, they are.
I don't know how he does it yet, but he's
been killing players in the real world.
That's insane. It's not.
Two people have been confirmed dead.
Where'd he go?
Kirito, watch the bridge for a sec.
I'm gonna check the scan and
see what name he's going by.
Yeah, you got it.
Huh?
Where is he?
Could he have moved that fast?
No.
This is our chance.
For what?
Your pal in the cloak isn't
showing up on the terminal.
My guess is he jumped in the river.
If I'm right, then he had to
disable his gear like you did.
What about his handgun?
He can still move underwater
with that equipped, right?
Even if he could, it's
just one little handgun.
I could take him out easy with my head.
You can't!
You saw what happened.
He used that little
gun to kill Pale Rider.
All it takes is one shot. Get it?
One shot and you're dead for real!
Yeah, well, I'm not buying it.
How's it even possible?
I mean, a player killing people IRL?
I know it sounds crazy,
but it's the truth.
This Death Gun guy killed a lot
of people in that VR MMO I was in.
When he used his sword on someone,
he knew he was really killing him.
And...
so did I.
There's a killer...
a murderer...
in GGO.
Xenon! Xenon!
I'm alright.
Just a little freaked out.
Anyway, I'm still not convinced
what you told me is possible.
But, I don't think you're
lying to me about it either.
That's good enough.
I can't ask for more yeah well we
better get out of the area asap.
The others know we're here
by now they think we're
busy fighting each other so
they'll be closing in soon.
you got a point we'll split
up here then wait what are
you gonna do i'm going after
death gun alone whatever
you do stay away from him
i'll keep my promise next
time we see each other i'll
give you the fight i owe you.
oh and one more thing
thanks for hearing me out.
just now instead of
shooting me
huh hey
wait for
me i'm coming with you
what that death gun guy
seems pretty tough and
if he kills you you won't
be able to fight me i
don't think you get out.
I'm not a fan of teaming up either,
but I think we stand a
better chance of knocking
that guy out of the game
if we work together.
No, I'm not down with that.
It's too dangerous.
We don't have any idea
where he'll pop up next,
so it'll be dangerous whether
we're together or not.
We better take care of this, Joker.
I'll block his bullets,
you wait for an opening.
Roger that.
It's all yours!
No way!
Death Gun's probably
heading north of the river.
I want to be there when he surfaces,
but I don't know where he'll stop.
Got any ideas, Sinon?
Uh...
I don't know if he's got
any other special skills,
but from what I've seen, he's a sniper.
He's going to avoid open spaces
and look for a place with cover.
If I were him, I'd set myself
up in the ruins of that city.
Good.
Then that's where you
and me are going to go.
I'm your six.
In SAO, we had a code.
Never let another player's
HP hit zero, no matter what.
We knew if it dropped to
nothing, that player would die.
Laughing Coffin didn't care.
They killed dozens,
no, hundreds of people.
The assault team had to step in.
They put a party together to
hunt them down, and capture them.
And Kazuto was there with you?
Yeah.
He was up front, going toe-to-toe.
Everything went to hell pretty fast.
Oh man, that's why Kazuto's
been acting so weird lately.
Now I'm worried.
Maybe he's trying to settle
some grudge or something.
Grudge?
Isn't this supposed to be a part-time job?
Sorry, I'm logging out for a bit. Why?
I have to get in touch
with Kirito's client.
Wait, he's got a client?
He's the one who got
Kirito to dive into GGO.
I bet he knows what's going on.
Oh, and Yui?
I'm going to need your
help while I'm gone.
Find out anything you can about GGO.
You can count on me, Mommy!
I'll be back in a little while.
Wish me luck.
Where the heck did he go?
You think we might have passed
him on the way over here?
No, we didn't pass him.
I was keeping an eye on the river
the whole time we were running.
Oh.
Well, the river dead ends here.
I guess he must be lurking
around somewhere in the city now.
Okay. Listen,
when his location pops
up in the next scan,
we'll rush him before
he can kill anyone else.
I'm done with that.
But there's one problem.
How will we know who Death Gun is?
I mean, that's not his
avatar's handle, remember?
Oh, yeah, right.
Then let's start with what we know.
You said you didn't recognize
the names of three new players.
It's not Pale Rider, that's for sure.
That leaves us with two names in play that
could be Death Gun, Jushi X, and Sterben.
If they're both in this city, we
can't afford to pick the wrong one.
Wait a sec.
I just thought of something.
In Japanese, the Shi in
Jushi means death, get it?
And the X could mean cross, like making
the sign of the cross, you think?
Or maybe it's too obvious.
Maybe not.
Aren't Avatar names
usually simple and obvious?
Mine's a variation on
my real name. And yours?
Yeah, same here.
Well, if they're both here,
we'll go after Jushi X first.
Oh, and if I get paralyzed
like Pale Rider, don't panic.
Get into position and wait.
Huh?
Deathgun's probably
hiding somewhere close.
When he comes out to finish me
off, that's when you shoot him.
Aren't you worried I'll shoot you, too?
Are you kidding?
You're the last person I'd
expect to play it like that.
Let's go, partner.
I'm counting on you.
Okay, but once we get
him, all bets are off!
Kirito, check the north side of the map.
It's him.
He's the only one in the city.
I guess he's our man, huh?
Yeah, I don't see Sterben around.
That settles it.
Jushi-X and Death Gun are one in the same.
That means he's going after...
...him.
We better move fast.
Rikoko's almost in range. Yeah.
Are you ready for this?
Yep.
Found him. Up there.
He's probably waiting for Rikoko
to walk right up into his sights.
I'll attack Jushi-X from
behind while I got the chance.
That building in front
of the stadium might
be a good place for you
to get into position.
No, I'm coming with you.
Not this time.
I can fight way better
knowing you got my back.
We're a team, remember?
Mm-hmm.
All I'm gonna need is 30 seconds to get up
there and I'll be ready to take him out.
Is that enough time for you?
Mm-hmm. Plenty.
Cool. See you in a bit.
As soon as Death Gun's gone,
we'll be enemies again.
I'll shoot him, beat
him, and then forget him.
Whatever.
It's not like I'll ever
see him again after this.
But Death Gun's supposed
to be in the stadium.
Kirito,
wherever you are, it's time I found out
if you were the real deal or a fake.
I remember how you fought
back then, all fury and rage.
If I kill this friend of yours,
and you go berserk like I remember,
I'll know it's really you.
He's gotta kill me?
Come on, Kirito.
Show me.
Let's see your fury, your
rage, your insane sword.
Show me for old time's sake.
My Type 54, Black Star.
It's the gun.
Why?
Why here?
Why does he have that gun?
Mijn...
... Mijn...
...
I want to be strong,
strong, strong, I want to
be proud of the sadness.
I've never been to the past.
I don't need one thing anymore.
I want to be strong and strong.
I want to be a dream.
I want to be a dream like a dream.
Next time, Death Chaser.
Here we go.